Alireza Mousavi Nezhad

Chief Information Security Officer

alirezamn93@gmail.com

https://alirezamn.me/

Shiraz, Iran

SUMMARY

I am a part time bug hunter and security consultant with 10+ years experience working with groups and companies such as Black Hat Group, Emperor Team, Tarahan Company, Tahlilgaran Company and Shiraz University of Medical Sciences.

EXPERIENCE

Chief Information Security Officer

04/2023 - Present

PrimeCo

- Monitoring and testing systems, servers and networks for vulnerabilities or indications of any security breaches.
- · Training other employees in your organization in cyber security and data safety.

Chief Information Security Officer

10/2013 - 04/2023

Tarahan

- Continuously evaluating and managing the company's cyber and technology risks.
- Developing and implementing processes and systems to prevent, detect, mitigate and recover from cyberattacks.

Security Consultants 03/2011 - 07/2015

Arvin Ide Dadeh Pad

- · Testing and analyzing assets for potential security threats.
- Identifying possible security threats and determining the best security measures.
- Designing, implementing, and maintaining security protocols, policies, plans, and systems to cover all possible security threats.

Pentester 04/2012 - 10/2014

Black Hat Group

- Developing Penetration Testing Tools
- · Penetration Testing Organizations and Companies

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering 2024

Islamic Azad University - Master

Pure Mathematics 2018

Shiraz University - Bachelor

SKILLS

C Programming Language Expert Rust Programming Language Intermediate

Python Programming Linux
Language Advanced

Windows Advanced

Expert

LANGUAGES

Persian Native English Intermediate